Finding Aid for the Edwin Hamlett Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Notecards:
  - Contacts: V (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Contacts: W (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Contacts: Y (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Contacts: Z (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Oversize Materials
  - The Trident Jacksonville High School, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Metro 1963-1971: Making it Work (Nashville Tennessean Supplement) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Martin Luther King Paddle Fan, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Foxfire Calendar, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Poster: Percentage of Nonwhite Population in Counties of Southern States, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Poster: Alabama Negro Population (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Poster: Leave the Cares of the City Behind (X3) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Poster: Trading with the Enemy, Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Poster: Tom Hayden: Report from Hanoi, Feb. 12, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Poster: Health Care and Hospitals in Easter Kentucky Public Hearing (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Poster: Southern Album Service (X2) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Poster: While America Sleeps (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Poster: National Welfare Organization Rights (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Poster: Youth Expo, Aug. 19-24 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Poster: the Draft and American Society, Feb. 15, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Poster: Uncle Sam Wants You Nigger (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Poster: Jesus Wanted (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Poster: The Draft: Service or Sentence (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Poster: $100 Billion Blackjack—the Civil Rights Bill (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Poster: Art Auction SCEF Benefit, Mar. 16, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bumper Sticker: Erase Chalk (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Bumper Sticker: One Man One Vote (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Bumper Sticker: Repeal the Draft (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Bumper Sticker: Boycott Grapes (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Bumper Sticker: America Love it? Then Liberate it (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Bumper Sticker: Vote for Hawkins For Governor (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Bumper Sticker: M.M. Roberts Must Go (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Bumper Sticker: M.M. Roberts Must Go (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Vietnam Oversized Paper (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - It’s Okay to Cry in the Office by John Poppy (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Poster; Join Us, Jan. 12, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - The Tulane Hullabaloo (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Inauguration, Jan 18-20 1969 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Council of Federated Organizations (COFO)/White Folks Project (WFP):
  - Correspondence: Contact Lists (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing and or Reports (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 10, 1964- May 19, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, May 22, 1964- Jun. 8, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jun. 10, 1964- Jun. 26, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Jun. 30, 1964- Aug 20, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 31, 1964- Feb. 4, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - General History (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - General History (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Finance Ledger (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Associates and Related Materials (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Guinan (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Guinan (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Guinan (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Guinan (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Reports (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Handwritten Reports, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Handwritten Reports, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Individual’s Reports, Mar. 6 1964- Jul. 22, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Individual’s Reports, Jul. 22, 1964- Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Applications 1964: Bailey- Hamlett (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Applications 1964: Henderson- Sorenson (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Applications 1964: Thrasher- Whitman (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Guides (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlets/Flyers (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Items (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Notes (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Anonymous Notebook (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Publications (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - “The House of Liberty” by Joyce Brown (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Federal Programs Project (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Workshops (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Highlander Workshop Materials 1965 (contains some SNCC as well) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Freedom Schools Materials (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - News Releases (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 15, Folder 22)
- COPA:
  - Contacts (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Outgoing (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Internal Memos (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Schedules (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Calendars (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - History/Organization General (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - History Organization Vermont/New York (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - History Organization Vermont/New York (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - History of Vermont/New York Youth Program (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Goals for Vermont/New York City Youth Project (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Non-YPV Camps (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Non-YPV Camps (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Resumes (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Drafts (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Blank Forms (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Pamphlets (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Book Lists (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Notes (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Proposals (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Flyers (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Vermont State Employees Contract and Materials (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Staff Materials (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Payroll, Jun. 27, 1968- Aug. 14, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Payroll, Aug. 15, 1968- Sept. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Expenses and Budget (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Rod Rogers Materials (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - YPV Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Transfers of Property (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Notes (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Notes (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Budget Related Notes (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Financial Notes (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Bills from Visiting Artists (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Notes (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Notes: Ripton (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Notes: Ripton (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Notes: Forest Service (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Notes from non-YPV Camps (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Institute for Policy Studies (IPS)
  - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - FCC Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - History (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Flyers/Booklets (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Statements/Reports (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Statements/Reports (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Reports: re FCC (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Reports: before the FCC (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Reports: Basic Policy Problems Pending before FCC (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Publications: ABL-ITT Merger Proceedings (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - FCC Releases, Apr. 1966- Apr. 1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - FCC Releases, Apr. 1967- Oct. 9, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - FCC Releases, Oct. 1967- Nov. 1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Seminars/Workshops (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Memos (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - News: Editorials to or in Major Newspapers (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Application Forms (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - News (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Notes: FCC (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Notes: Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Mississippi Schools Materials:
  - Proposals (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Court Cases (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Flyers/Pamphlets (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - MSVC Materials (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - MSVC Materials (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Mississippi Official and Statistical Register, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Statistical Data, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Statistical Data, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Statistics (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Statistics and Reports (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - School Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Reports (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - “Non-Public Schools”, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Close-Up, Jun. 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Kemper County Messenger, Dec. 1969- Mar. 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Economic Highlights of Mississippi (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Handbook of Selected Data for Mississippi (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Assorted (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Academic Freedom and Tenure (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Public Schools in Mississippi, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Teacher Supply and Demand, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Special Report on Augusta Georgia and Jackson St. University (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Financing Mississippi Public Schools, Jan. 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Publications: ESEA Evaluation, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Expenditures per Pupil, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Majority-Black School Districts, Jul. 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Our Town is Different (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Publications: News and Views, May 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Advance, Nov. 1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Advance, Dec. 1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Advance, Jan. 1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Advance, Feb. 1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Advance, Mar. 1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Washington County Paper (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Public School Enrollment, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Alcorn College Materials (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Greenville Materials (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Greenville Public School Materials (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings, Mostly Editorials (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Kemper County Paper (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Field Reports (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Various County Reports (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Reports/Notes (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Notes: MVSC (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Notes: Alcorn College (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Notes (Box 22, Folder 20)
- South Carolina Schools Materials:
  - Director’s Report (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Proposal for Continuing Desegregation (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Proposal Continuing Special Institute for Desegregation (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Publications: “Your Schools” Newsletter (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Publications: “Your Schools” Newsletter (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Publications: 1960/1970 Leadership Handbook (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Publications: 1960/1970 Directory; 1969 Legislative Manual (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Multiple (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Dawn of a New Decade 1970’s (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Negro in America (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Publications: 1968/1969 Superintendent Report (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Superintendent’s 100 year Report and Library Services Catalogue (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Welfare/the Perpetuation of Poverty (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Sandlapper, Jan. 1970 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Technical Education in South Carolina 1969 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Economic Profile of Allendale County (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Publications: School Desegregation Legal Decision (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Surveys and Questionnaires (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Flyers and pamphlets (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Drafts: Williamsburg County (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Drafts: Fairfield County (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers: Allendale County (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Allendale County Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Drafts: Allendale County (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Notes: Allendale County (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Notes: Allendale County (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Notes: Fairfield County (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Notes: Fairfield County (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Williamsburg County Materials (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Williamsburg County Schools Summary (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Williamsburg County Proposal for Education Professions Development Act (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Notes: Williamsburg County (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Notes: Williamsburg Country (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Notes: Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Nursing Materials:
  - Nursing License (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Crisis Intervention Resource Directory, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Contacts (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Graduation Letters (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Class Materials (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tests (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - License (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Reports (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - American Nursing Association (ANA) Materials (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - ANA materials -Homosexuality (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Arkansas Nursing Handbook 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Arkansas Nursing Handbook 2 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Arkansas Nursing Handbook 3 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Arkansas Children’s Unit Materials (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Arkansas Children’s Unit Materials (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Arkansas Children’s Unit Materials (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas Children’s Unit Materials (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Arkansas Children’s Unit Materials (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Hospital Materials (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cumberland Psychiatric Hospital Handbook (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cumberland Psychiatric Hospital (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Cumberland Psychiatric Hospital (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Cumberland Psychiatric Hospital (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cumberland Psychiatric Hospital (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - District 3 (Tennessee) Materials (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - District 3 (Tennessee) Materials (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - District 3 (Tennessee) Materials (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - District 3 (Tennessee) Evaluations (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Recruitment and Retention Committee (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Recruitment and Retention Meeting Minutes (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Recruitment and Retention Agendas Proposals (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Recruitment and Retention Performance Evaluation (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Recruitment and Retention Staff Survey (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Recruitment and Retention Staff Survey (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Recruitment and Retention Survey Results (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (1) (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (2) (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (3) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (4) (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (5) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (6) (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (7) (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report 1988 (8) (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Recruitment and Retention Notes (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Articles (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Publications (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Publications (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Publications (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Publications (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Publications (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Publications (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Re-evaluate Counseling Notes (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Systematics Employee Handbook (1) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Systematics Employee Handbook (2) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Tennessee Nurses Association (TNA)/ American Nurses Association (ANA) Application (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - TNA Bylaws, Oct. 1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - TNA Bylaws, Oct. 1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - TNA General (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - TNA General (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - TNA CERP Continuing Education (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - TNA Psych (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - TNA Psych (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - TNA Miscellaneous Materials (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - TNA Miscellaneous Materials (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - TNA Miscellaneous Materials (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - TNA Miscellaneous Materials (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - TNA Convention, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - TNA Convention, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - TNA Convention, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - TNA Convention, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - TNA Convention, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - TNA Convention, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - TNA Convention, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - TNA Convention, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - TNA Council on Practice, (1979) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - TNA Council on Practice, (1979) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - TNA Council on Practice, (1979) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - TNA Council on Practice, (1979) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - TNA Council on Practice, (1979) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - TNA Alert, Feb. 1977- Dec. 1978 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Vanderbilt Employee Handbook, Feb. 1 1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Vanderbilt Medical Center: About VUMC Booklet (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Vanderbilt Nursing Orientation Material (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Vanderbilt Nursing Staff Handbook, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Vanderbilt Nursing Service Brochure (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbilt Patient Orientation (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Vanderbilt Staff Manual (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Vanderbilt Health Coalition (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Vanderbilt Patients Rights and Advocacy Materials (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Vanderbilt Proposals (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Vanderbilt Resolutions (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Vanderbilt Resolutions (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Vanderbilt Reports (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Vanderbilt Communiqués, Receipts, etc… (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Vanderbilt Conference Agendas (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Vanderbilt Conference on Nursing and the Homosexual Patient (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Vanderbilt Miscellaneous Materials (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Vanderbilt Miscellaneous Materials (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Nursing Pamphlets (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Nursing Pamphlets (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - AHA Protocol (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Guide to Primary Health Care Services of Nashville and Davidson County, (1977) (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Guide to Primary Health Care Services of Nashville and Davidson County (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1199 NLN Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - NSG (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Health Advantage Materials (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Health Fair Materials (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Health Movement Organization (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - In-service Education Packs (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Learning Experience Guide (1) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Learning Experience Guide (2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Learning Experience Guide (3) (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Learning Experience Guide (4) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Learning Experience Guide (5) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Stress Materials (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Articles: The Big Wheel 89-118 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Articles: The Big Wheel 119-132 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Articles: The Big Wheel 133-152 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Articles: The Big Wheel 153-160 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Articles: Hospital Hazards (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Publications: 1199 News, September 1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Publications: 1199 NLN News, Jan/Feb 1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Publications: American Druggist, Oct. 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Publications: American Journal of Nursing, May 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Publications: American Journal of Nursing, Aug 1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Publications: American Journal of Nursing, Jan 1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Publications: American Journal of Nursing, Dec. 1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Publications: American Journal of Nursing, Jun. 1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Feb Mar 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Apr May 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Jun Jul 1977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Aug. Sept. 1977 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Oct. Nov. Dec. 1977 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Jan. Feb. 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Publications: American Nurse, May. July Aug. 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Sept. Oct. 1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Nov. 1978 Jan 1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Feb. Mar. 1979 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Apr. May 1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Jun. Aug. 1979 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Nov. 1979 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Jan. 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Mar. 1980 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Jan. 1983 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Publications: American Nurse, Apr. 1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Publications: ANA, Feb. 1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Better Nutrition, Dec. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Guidance Counselor’s Handbook 3rd Ed. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Heal Yourself (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Health Activist’s Digest Fall, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Health Activist’s Digest Fall, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Health Pak Bulletin, May 1969, Dec 1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Health Pak Bulletin, Dec 1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Human Behavior (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Life Begins Every Day (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Look at Legislation, Jan-Mar 1989 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Medical World News, Apr. 30 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Publications: News and Views, Oct 1972- Jan 1974 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Publications: News and Views, Feb 1974- Dec 1974 (and Over VU may 1980) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Publications: News and Views, Jan. 1975-Sept. 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Publications: News and Views, Aug. Sept. Oct 1976 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Publications: News and Views, Jun.-Dec. 1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Publications: News and Views, Mar. 1977- Aug 1977 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Publications: News and Views, Sept. 1977- Holiday Edition 1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Publications: News and Views, Jan.-Mar. 1980 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Nurse Educator, May-Jun. 1980 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Nursing Management, Oct. 1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, Nov./Dec. 1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, May/Jun. 1978 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, Nov./Dec. 1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, Jan./Feb. 1979 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, May/Jun. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, Mar. 1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, Apr. 1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Occupational Health, May 1980 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Present Time: 22 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Publications: Present Time: 26 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Present Time: 27 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Publications: Present Time: 28 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Present Time: 29 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Present Time: 31 (Box 40, Folder 10)